Next step, with a nice, even coat of media on your photocopy, flip it over.
Take your hand and I want this thing stuck, stuck, stuck, stuck on here.
Everything should be stuck, every single surface of it, no edges poking up.
If they are, have some media on the end of your brush, gently go around like that, and then there you go, then press it down.
Now as soon as you feel you have a good seal, you're not done yet, because you want to put some more media.
I like putting some more media on the back of the photocopy as well.
Some people don't do this, to me actually the transfers are a little more consistent when you do.
So, same as last time, put a bunch of dots on the back, now we're going to do the same thing.
Nice, even strokes.
I prefer a bigger brush for this, not like a little one, otherwise you can see it can take a while, and media does dry, so you want to make sure you have a nice, even layer on here, before the drying process starts, which will be about five to ten minutes after first application.
There.